

### Sachin Gevariya

Full Stack Ruby On Rails Professional

Professional Ruby On Rails Developer with more than 6 years of experience in Ruby On Rails Development. Involved in requirement gathering, architect design of the product as well as database and servers, coding and TDD and BDD testing with releases.

s.gevariya@gmail.com

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

in linkedin.com/in/sachingevariya

+91-8866572265

sachingevariya.com 🚍

Sachingevariya

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Founder & Technical Director | Full Stack Ruby On Rails Professional

**Essence Solusoft** 

09/2016 – Present Ahmedabad

# **Sr. Architect | Full Stack Ruby On Rails Developer** Bacancy Technology Pvt. Ltd.

01/2016 – 09/2016 Ahmedabad

Achievements/Tasks

 Handling requirement gathering and software architect design along with DB Schema and servers

Handled multiple team leader with small teams of 2-4

## Sr. Software Engineer | Full Stack Ruby On Rails Developer

Solute Technolabs LLP

10/2014 - 01/2016

Ahmedabad

Achievements/Tasks

- Finished more than 5 successful products like RemedySocial,
  FitnessQuotient, 7Dailymoves, Barkloudly and many more
- Learned server level knowledge deeply from various projects and increased server security

# **Lead Ruby On Rails Developer** Bacancy Technology Pvt. Ltd.

07/2012 – 09/2014

Ahmedabad

Modasa

Achievements/Tasks

- Self learned ROR as first ROR Employee in company
- Handling multiple projects and increased quality of product by 50%

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Alumni Member (06/2006 - Present)

Foundation For Excellence

Alumni Member (01/2010 - Present)

Fusion Study Foundation, United Way of Baroda

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor in Computer Engineering**

G.E.C. Modasa (G.T.U.)

05/2008 – 05/2012

#### **SKILLS**

Ruby On Rails

ReactJS

AngularJS

DevOps

Cloud Services (AWS, Google Cloud, DigitalOcean, Engine yard and many more)

PostgreSQL

MySQL

MongoDB

HTML + JQuery

#### PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN

Collect Plus (Shopify App)

https://apps.shopify.com/collectplus

Order Tagger (Shopify App)

https://apps.shopify.com/ordertagger

Customer Tagger (Shopify App)

https://apps.shopify.com/customer-tagger

Reelo

https://www.reelo.in/

My Property Build

https://app.mypropertybuild.com

7 Daily Moves (API Development)

On Google and ios playstore

Atomized

https://www.atomized.com/

Earnings cast

https://earningscast.com/

Tennis League Network

https://www.tennisnortheast.com/

Budget Plug-in (Redmine)

https://projekt.danva.dk/login

#### **LANGUAGES**

English





Hindi



Gujarati

